Let's look at Google interviews and let's see what you can find.
There is a long building on which there are 100 islands.
That is, there are hundreds of floors from one to 100.
Now, there is a special floor called N number.
If something falls from that floor, it will break.
But if it falls from the lower floor, it will not break.
And what we have given is that we have given 2 special undying.
If we fall from the upper floor, it will break.
But if it falls from the lower floor, it will not break.
We have to know that for any value of N,
if we only use 2 eggs and find out what N is,
then I will have to fall from the lower floor as many times as possible.
And then, you will get 1 second of the last one.
But if you find out before that, then I will comment below and tell you.
Today, we will meet again in the next video.
Till then, keep learning and keep exploring.